<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Japari Parkman</title>
    <description>A Kemono Friends Pacman modification.</description>
    <link>http://seedmanc.github.io/japari-parkman</link>
    <atom:link href="http://seedmanc.github.io/japari-parkman/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 21:24:00 +0300</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en</language>
    
      <item>
        <title>Closed beta is out</title>
        <description>
			After months of development and over a hundred commits, my game finally reaches the closed beta test stage.
	        Expect a public release within a week.
		</description>
        <link>http://seedmanc.github.io/japari-parkman</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://seedmanc.github.io/japari-parkman</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 23:26:05 +0300</pubDate>
           
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>First public release</title>
        <description>
			The game is finally ready.
		</description>
        <link>http://seedmanc.github.io/japari-parkman</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://seedmanc.github.io/japari-parkman</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 21:24:00 +0300</pubDate>

        <category>update</category>

      </item>

      <item>
        <title>Update 1.1 is live</title>
        <description>
           This update addresses the most reported problems with the game, such as doubled speed on monitors with high FPS, excess difficulty due to the level resetting upon player's death and performance issues.
		    Now you have the option to limit FPS to 60 to keep the speed at the intended level and the eaten dots will not reappear, making the implementation closer to that of the original Pacman.
           Note however that this change reduces the potential highscores by half of what was possible in version 1. Previous highscores in the TOP 10 list were adjusted to accomodate that.
           On top of that I implemented the basic mobile support, the game can be controlled by taps on the field, summons are available by their respective icons. Playability has been tested on Android Chrome and Firefox.
           Aside from that there are numerous cosmetic fixes and bugs resolved.
        </description>
        <link>https://seedmanc.github.io/japari-parkman/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://seedmanc.github.io/japari-parkman</guid>
		 <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 12:46:00 +0300</pubDate>

        <category>update</category>

      </item>

      <item>
        <title>Parkman backup hostings</title>
        <description>
           In case the main url, https://seedmanc.github.io/japari-parkman/ ever goes down, I provide a couple of mirrors for it.
            Here's two:

            http://anoneko.gitlab.io/japari-parkman - it was originally intended as the main one, but gitlab has proven to be unstable so I had to migrate back to GH. Currently redirects to it.\n
            http://seedmanc.tumblr.com/japari-parkman - not tested much  

            And of course you can drop by my twitter https://twitter.com/Seedmanc and ask personally for help if any problem arises.
            Speaking about which, I'm very curious as to how many people even receive these updates via RSS. If you're reading this, please contact me in any way you find convenient to report that this message has reached you.
        </description>
        <link>https://seedmanc.github.io/japari-parkman/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://seedmanc.github.io/japari-parkman</guid>
		 <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 20:44:00 +0300</pubDate>

        <category>update</category>

      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
